Register of the Ann Meader diary
Hoover Institution Archives
Ann Meader diary
1933-1975
74073
Hoover Institution Archives
2 manuscript boxes (0.8 linear feet)
The Ann Meader diary relates to conditions of daily life in England during World War II. Includes biographical materials, correspondence, other writings, and photographs.
Meader, Ann, 1899-
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1974.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Biographical Note
British author.
Scope and Content of Collection
The Ann Meader diary relates to conditions of daily life in England during World War II. Includes personal diary with daily accounts, biographical material, correspondence, other writings, and some photographs.
World War, 1939-1945--Great Britain.; Great Britain--History--George VI, 1936-1952.
- Biographical File, 1970, 1974 (Box-folder 1: 1)
  Scope and Contents note
  Newspaper clippings about Ann Meader.
- War Diary, 1939-1946
  - Excerpt, 1946 (Box-folder 1: 2)
  - "File I,", 1939 September 3 - 1940 December 31 (Box-folder 1: 3)
  - "File II,", 1941 January 1 - December 1 (Box-folder 1: 4-5)
  - "File III,", 1942 January 1 - December 1 (Box-folder 1: 6-7)
  - "File IV,", 1943 January 1 - December 31 (Box-folder 1: 8-9)
  - "File V,", 1944 January 1 - December 31 (Box-folder 2: 1)
  - "File VI,", 1946 January 1 - April 12 (Box-folder 2: 2-3)
- Correspondence, 1975
  - National Library of Australia, 1975 (Box-folder 2: 4)
  - Public Archives of Canada, 1975 (Box-folder 2: 5)
- Writings, Phantoms of Scotland, 1973 (Box-folder 2: 6)
- Photographs, 1933-1975 (Box-folder 2: 7)
  Includes portraits of Ann Meader and photographs of her family members.